Jinghui,
why did you run away?
Senior Sister,
I won't do it again.
Please forgive me.
Don't let them hit me anymore.
Running away secretly
and lacking true cultivation.
Punish her.
I've already sent
many people to look for her,
and the police are all out.
But I don't think they are reliable now.
Little bandit,
hurry up and find a way to save Senior Sister.
Don't worry.
Yesterday, I found a
very strange carriage track.
I followed this track
and traced it all the way here.
A track?
Are you sure she was
taken away by a carriage?
This is the only clue we have now.
We must investigate it no matter what.
Sir,
did you see a carriage
pass by here last night?
Sir,
around 10:00 PM.
The hour of Hai.
Did you hear
any strange noises?
I can't hear you.
How are we supposed to investigate now?
Calm down.
There must be some clue
that we overlooked.
Stop hitting me.
Do you know what rules
Jinghui has violated?
Jinghui
has been completely Westernized.
Not only
does she eat Western food and live in a Western-style house,
but she also took a Western name and converted to a Western religion.
She has practiced under the Heavenly Lord for a year,
but she remains unteachable.
She must be eliminated.
Alas,
boundless holy law,
Heavenly Lord Jumang,
enlighten the ignorant,
and eliminate the evil.
Today, your disciple returns to eliminate the evil,
and deliver the wicked Jinghui
to the Pure Land.
Alas,
boundless holy law,
Heavenly Lord Jumang
descends here.
You disciples do not think of enlightenment,
nor do you think of mercy.
You kill in vain,
violate my will,
and go against my purpose.
Do you know your sins?
All disciples, kneel and listen to the decree.
Disciple Jinghui has committed grave sins,
but the gods of the nine heavens
subdue demons and monsters.
Jinghui can still be saved,
and must not be killed in vain.
Your disciple
will obey the decree.
My head hurts so much.
What happened?
Master.
I don't know what happened just now.
My head hurts so much.
I don't remember anything.
You just said some strange things.
No wonder I felt like
I was controlled by
an unknown force.
As for what happened next,
I don't remember.
You were possessed by the Heavenly Lord,
conveyed his decree,
and saved Jinghui.
That was the Heavenly Lord manifesting.
You may leave now.
Yes.
Here.
Eat something first.
Thank you.
Do you know where we are?
Then do you know the way out?
Every cave entrance here is guarded.
It's heavily guarded.
We can't get out at all.
I was spotted as soon as I reached the entrance.
Rest and recover here.
I will get you out.
How can we escape?
It seems my partners haven't found this place.
I have to rely on myself.
Here.
Do you see these wheel tracks?
Isn't that the deaf-mute old man?
There's something wrong with that old man.
What's wrong?
The villagers here
usually pack their carts full of vegetables to sell.
Why did he come back with vegetables?
Besides,
can he finish all these by himself?
Wontons!
Freshly made hot wontons!
Little Zhou's wonton stall is at the West Gate.
The distance from Binjiang Road to the West Gate is five kilometers.
The carriage traveled for about 20 minutes.
The carriage's speed should be 15 kilometers per hour.
After leaving the city, it went west,
traveled for about half an hour,
then turned north,
entered a rugged path,
and arrived at the destination.
This should be near the suburbs.
In all my life,
I never knew there was
such a big cave in the suburbs.
Where on earth is this?
Wait.
Jingming.
Master.
Follow me.
Today, I saw the carriage that took the people
was covered in a kind of red soil.
It's a leached brown soil
unique to the Baxian Mountain area in the suburbs.
If I'm not mistaken,
this is near Baxian Mountain.
That's not right.
When they were burning things that day,
I clearly didn't see my necklace.
Where did it go?
Strange.
Could she have stolen it?
Somebody!
Find it quickly!
You guys,
guard this place well.
Don't let a single fly out.
Let's go search over there.
There's more to this courtyard than meets the eye.
Senior Sister must have been taken by them.
Little bandit.
Let's go save Senior Sister.
Hold on.
Look.
They are all wearing uniforms.
They look like cult members.
It's a bit dangerous.
Let's go back and discuss it.
Jingxin.
What's wrong, Senior Sister?
Where did you just go?
I was sleeping.
Impossible.
You two, get up.
Did you see her go out?
Senior Sister, we were all sleeping.
We didn't see anything.
Impossible.
Senior Sister,
the Venerable wants you to go over.
You just wait.
All right.
I know.
Okay.
How is it, my lady?
Did you find the person?
Not yet.
I'm pacing around anxiously.
How can you still be so calm?
Superintendent Li,
but we found a clue.
Then what are we waiting for?
Hurry up and find Detective Jiang.
But it's dangerous to go.
The two of us aren't enough.
Superintendent Li, you must know
Detective Jiang acted as bait
for the sake of the whole city.
Please send reinforcements, Superintendent Li.